reflexmath.com 2011-11-08

# Reflex : Privacy Policy

We are committed to our users privacy. This privacy policy covers the site http://www.reflexmath.com and contains the following information: 

  1. The personally identifiable information (PIN) ExploreLearning collects. 
  2. The PIN that third parties collect through the ExploreLearning web site. 
  3. The name(s) of organization(s) collecting the information. 
  4. How ExploreLearning uses the information. 
  5. Entities with whom ExploreLearning may share PIN. 
  6. The choices available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of PIN. 
  7. The security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of PIN under ExploreLearning control. 
  8. Ways that users can correct any inaccuracies in their PIN. 

#### Information Collection and Use 

ExploreLearning collects information at several different points on the ExploreLearning web site and is the sole owner of all infomation that is collected. 

We generally use the aggregate data we collect to evaluate the extent to which the ExploreLearning websites continue to be useful and relevant to our members and the general public. For example, we may perform statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our members and visitors, to measure overall user demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the ExploreLearning domain and to analyze how and where to use our resources. A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last uri requested and browser type), interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image), navigation and click-stream data (passive activity such as pages visited), unique identifiers (login id or other id), interactive data (account activity and searches performed), navigation and click-stream data (passive activity such as pages visited), online contact information (email address), unique identifiers (login id or other id), search terms (search text), transaction information (account transactions), user's name, user's login information, user's employer, organization department user is employed, user's job title, business/organization name and department/division of business/organization. It is optional for the user to provide User's Name, User's Login Information, User's Employer, Organization Department User is Employed, User's Job Title, Business/Organization Name and Department/Division of Business/Organization. We encourage users to provide optional information so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. The reason we use this information is to complete the current transaction, contact by email or regular mail, enhance our site and product offerings, maintain and secure our site and understand (in aggregate) interests of website visitors. We retain this information as stated by our business practices. When users have data collected for the purpose of contacting by email or regular mail, they are given the opportunity to opt-out of information collected (Please see our Choice and Opt-out section). 

##### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie according to the following information. 

  * IE, see [Microsoft's Internet Explorer Web Privacy](http://www.microsoft.com/windows/ie/evaluation/overview/privacy.asp) page.
  * Firefox privacy policy. <http://www.mozilla.com/en-US/legal/privacy/firefox.html>
  * Safari privacy policy. <http://www.apple.com/safari/features.html>

Our website uses cookies to enhance our site. 

#### Profiles 

ExploreLearning does not create a user profile. 

#### Communications from the Site

When customers provide us contact information for User Group 1 (users can opt-out by following the directions in our 'Choice' section) we use the information to contact the user to deliver sales and product information that will be useful to the them. 

#### Sharing Information 

##### Legal Disclaimer 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

##### Personally Identifiable Information 

Personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties. 

##### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) 

Aggregate information is not shared with any third parties. 

#### Choice/Opt-out 

When our web site originates email, our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of these communications by one of 2 methods:

  1. following the unsubscribe link located near the bottom of every email they receive, or
  2. by emailing us at support@reflexmath.com from the email address they wish to be unsubscribed.

#### Data Security 

ExploreLearning has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company uses secure encryption technology (secure socket connection) for all sensitive financial or health data transmitted on our site. 

#### Visitors Under 13 Years of Age 

ExploreLearning collects personally identifiable information online from a child under 13 without any parental consent. 

#### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address) they can change all information. If a user wishes to correct/update information or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy. 

#### Links and Advertisements 

Our website contains links to other sites. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We, ExploreLearning, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

#### Changes to the Privacy Statement 

The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. If we significantly change our policy, we will post a notice in a conspicuous place on our website notifying visitors of policy changes. 

#### Data Retention Statement

Stated Business Practices Data retention - We keep information about you and your purchases for as long as you remain our customer. 

#### Contact Information 

Using the following information, you can contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy.   

ExploreLearning   
P.O. Box 2185   
Charlottesville, VA 22902   
USA 

E-mail: support@reflexmath.com

Phone: 434-293-7043 

#### Resolving Privacy Policy Disputes

If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, please contact us for resolution.
